Let's take a look at some example code that shows when implicit conversions happen,
让我们来看一些示例代码，这些代码显示了隐式转换何时发生，
and how you have to be careful about types.
以及如何谨慎对待类型。
First, we make an int called nHrs and initialize it to 40.
首先，我们创建一个名为 NHR 的整数并将其初始化为 40。
Next, we make nDays and initialize it to seven.
接下来，我们创作 nDays 并将其初始化为 7。
Next, we have a float called average,
接下来，我们有一个名为平均值的浮点数，
which is initialized to nHours divided by nDays.
它被初始化为 nHours 除以 nDays。
Both nHours and nDays are ints so this is integer division.
nHours 和 nDays 都是整数，所以这是整数除法。
We have 40 divided by seven,
我们有 40 除以七
which for integer division results in five.
，对于整数除法，则得出五。
Now since we are assigning an int to a float,
现在，由于我们要为浮点数赋值 int，
the compiler will implicitly convert that integer result to a floating point number.
编译器会将该整数结果隐式转换为浮点数。
But it does that after the division,
但是它是在除法之后这样做的，
so we end up initializing average with a value of 5.0.
所以我们最终将平均值初始化为5.0。
Then we print out that 40 hours in 7 days is 5.0 hours per day.
然后我们打印出 7 天内 40 小时等于每天 5.0 小时。
This is not the right answer,
这不是正确的答案，
so let's fix this code.
所以让我们修复这段代码。
Here we've made one small change to the code.
在这里，我们对代码做了一个小改动。在@@
We have explicitly cast nDays to a float before we do the division,
进行除法之前，我们已经明确将 nDay
which is called out with the red underline here.
s 转换为浮点数，此处用红色下划线标出。
We start the same way,
我们以同样的方式开始，
nHours is created and initialized to 40,
nHours 被创建并初始化为 40，
and nDays is created and initialized to seven.
nDays 被创建并初始化为 7。
However, now things go differently.
但是，现在情况有所不同。
The divisor of this expression is now seven cast to a float,
这个表达式的除数现在是七转换为浮点数，
so we need to evaluate the integer 40 divided by the floating point numbers 7.0.
所以我们需要计算整数 40 除以浮点数 7.0。
Computers divide integers by integers
计算机将整数除以整数
or floating point numbers by floating point numbers,
或将浮点数除以浮点数，
so the compiler has to implicitly convert
因此编译器在进行除法
40 to a floating point number before doing the division.
之前必须将 40 隐式转换为浮点数。
Now we are doing floating point division,
现在我们正在进行浮点除法，
14.0 divided by 7.0 equals 5.71.
14.0 除以 7.0 等于 5.71。
We now initialize average with this value which means that when we print out our results,
现在，我们用这个值初始化平均值，这意味着当我们打印出结果时，
we get the correct answer.
我们会得到正确的答案。
Now you have seen both implicit conversions as well as explicit casts.
现在你已经看到了隐式转换和显式转换。
Casting is something you use when you need to.
当你需要时，你可以使用铸造。
However, you should use it sparingly,
但是，
only when you think through what you are converting between and why.
只有当你仔细考虑要在什么之间进行转换以及为什么要转换时，才应该谨慎使用它。